<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>code on rds</title>
    <link>https://rahuldshetty.github.io/tags/code/</link>
    <description>Recent content in code on rds</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rahuldshetty.github.io/tags/code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I created my own Programming Language ?</title>
      <link>https://rahuldshetty.github.io/blog/how-i-created-my-own-programming-lanaguage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rahuldshetty.github.io/blog/how-i-created-my-own-programming-lanaguage/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Programming languages are nothing but programs written by other programmers for you to program your programs. These days developers take programming language for granted, not everyone are interested in understanding the complexity that goes behind a simple &amp;ldquo;Hello world&amp;rdquo; program until they run into issue for their complex program where they need to start digging into the Source code program to find out why there is a weird Null Pointer Exception or memory leak happening in the code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using ReactJS &amp; TensorflowJS for Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://rahuldshetty.github.io/blog/using-reactjs-tensorflowjs-for-text-classification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rahuldshetty.github.io/blog/using-reactjs-tensorflowjs-for-text-classification/</guid>
      <description>Live Demo: Indian Name Classification
Source Code: Github
Python Code: Notebook
Intro to Text Classification Often times human use logic and knowledge to analyze different things. For Example, A botanist could identify and name different species of plants than a normal person. While the normal person could use logic to say how plants differ based on their shape, size and color of the leaves. This problem of identifying the class/category of any object is known as Classification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create binary search tree in Python3?</title>
      <link>https://rahuldshetty.github.io/blog/how-to-create-binary-search-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 02:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rahuldshetty.github.io/blog/how-to-create-binary-search-tree/</guid>
      <description>What are Binary Search Trees? This will by my first topic on which I will be showing you guys on how to implement a binary search tree datastructre(DS) and go through the basic fundamentals.
So a Binary Search Tree (BST) is a type of graph data structrue where you have many nodes arranged in a reversed tree fashion. Each node starting from the top (which is called as root node) is split into two sub trees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
